<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Everybody's Talking Therapy</title><link>https://www.everybodystalkingtherapy.ca/</link><description>Recent content on Everybody's Talking Therapy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>emma.fackelmann@gmail.com (Emma Fackelmann)</managingEditor><webMaster>emma.fackelmann@gmail.com (Emma Fackelmann)</webMaster><copyright>© Emma Fackelmann</copyright><atom:link href="https://www.everybodystalkingtherapy.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.everybodystalkingtherapy.ca/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>emma.fackelmann@gmail.com (Emma Fackelmann)</author><guid>https://www.everybodystalkingtherapy.ca/about/</guid><description>Owner &amp; Psychotherapist Emma Fackelmann
Emma is the founder of Everybody&amp;rsquo;s Talking and is currently the head psychotherapist. Over the past nine years, she has worked in mental health and addictions, furthering her career development in psychotherapy since 2018. Her theoretical practices are integratively grounded in trauma-informed care, humanistic, existential, psychodynamic, person-centered, biopsychosocial, and attachment theories. She incorporates technical elements eclectically to suit the needs of her clients; a few examples of therapy modalities she practices include:</description></item><item><title>Becoming a Client</title><link>https://www.everybodystalkingtherapy.ca/becoming_a_client/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>emma.fackelmann@gmail.com (Emma Fackelmann)</author><guid>https://www.everybodystalkingtherapy.ca/becoming_a_client/</guid><description>Becoming a Client</description></item><item><title>Booking and Fees</title><link>https://www.everybodystalkingtherapy.ca/booking_and_fees/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>emma.fackelmann@gmail.com (Emma Fackelmann)</author><guid>https://www.everybodystalkingtherapy.ca/booking_and_fees/</guid><description>Booking To book an initial 15 minute consultation, please book here.
Fees 50 minute independent session - $135 plus taxes 30 minute - $70 plus taxes 50 minute student session - $95 plus taxes I have a number of sliding scale openings starting as low as $75 plus taxes
Currently accepting payments as E-transfers. My psychotherapy services can be covered by certain insurance companies, please review this with your specific company .</description></item><item><title>In a Crisis</title><link>https://www.everybodystalkingtherapy.ca/in_a_crisis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>emma.fackelmann@gmail.com (Emma Fackelmann)</author><guid>https://www.everybodystalkingtherapy.ca/in_a_crisis/</guid><description> I am not a crisis responder and my services are focused on assisting clients that are not actively experiencing suicidal tendencies.
If you are currently experiencing a crisis, the following resources may prove useful:
Distress Center Halton Distress Center Niagara Community Resources Barrett Centre for Crisis Support Crisis Outreach and Support Team</description></item><item><title>Resources in a pinch</title><link>https://www.everybodystalkingtherapy.ca/resources_in_a_pinch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>emma.fackelmann@gmail.com (Emma Fackelmann)</author><guid>https://www.everybodystalkingtherapy.ca/resources_in_a_pinch/</guid><description>These are a few helpful resources I often recommend:
The Upward Spiral by Alex Korb, PhD is great for those who notice themselves spiralling down or are diagnosed with depression (I find the information to be universal 😊) First, We Make the Beast Beautiful: A New Journey Through Anxiety, by Sarah Wilson explains the beauty of accepting certain parts of ourselves, specifically focusing on anxiety Building a gratitude list — sometimes shifting our perspective to the positive uplifts our spirits, it’s simple and effective!</description></item></channel></rss>